{
    "name": "Italian Adjectives",
    "vocab": [
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "stretto",
            "failed": 11,
            "lastAsked": 1519238005.8992233,
            "question": "narrow",
            "tried": 15
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "thick",
            "failed": 10,
            "lastAsked": 1519237995.6280553,
            "question": "spesso",
            "tried": 14
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "bagnato",
            "failed": 11,
            "lastAsked": 1519238008.1517172,
            "question": "wet",
            "tried": 15
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "weak",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1519237981.412215,
            "question": "debole",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "straniero",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1519237956.1716585,
            "question": "foreign",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "empty",
            "failed": 9,
            "lastAsked": 1519237997.651898,
            "question": "vuoto",
            "tried": 13
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "few",
            "failed": 8,
            "lastAsked": 1519237999.2756712,
            "question": "pochi",
            "tried": 12
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "buio",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1519237986.8363178,
            "question": "dark",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "narrow",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1519238040.555701,
            "question": "stretto",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "i gusti",
            "failed": 9,
            "lastAsked": 1519238085.5146973,
            "question": "tastes",
            "tried": 13
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "debole",
            "failed": 9,
            "lastAsked": 1519238087.7622647,
            "question": "weak",
            "tried": 13
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "pochi",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1519238060.9834518,
            "question": "few",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "incorrect"
            ],
            "answer": "wrong",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1519238029.7038565,
            "question": "sbagliato",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "molti",
            "failed": 7,
            "lastAsked": 1519238083.5464885,
            "question": "many",
            "tried": 11
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "molto",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1519238015.887297,
            "question": "much",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "corretto",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1519238058.4468942,
            "question": "correct",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "slow",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1519238111.8263435,
            "question": "lento",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "bitter",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1519238092.6349573,
            "question": "amaro",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "some",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1519238128.0663376,
            "question": "alcuni",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "pesante",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1519238105.9705389,
            "question": "heavy",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "spesso",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1519238113.970373,
            "question": "thick",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "amaro",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1519238130.2945628,
            "question": "bitter",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "wide",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1519238090.2341855,
            "question": "ampio",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "alcuni",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1519238126.594618,
            "question": "some",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dritto",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1519238150.5055397,
            "question": "straight",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "secco",
            "failed": 6,
            "lastAsked": 1519238168.001837,
            "question": "dry",
            "tried": 10
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "dimensioni"
            ],
            "answer": "dimensioni (or) misure",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1519238147.594488,
            "question": "sizes",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "poco",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1519238153.0738735,
            "question": "little",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "pulito",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1519238163.2500384,
            "question": "clean",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "potente",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1519238169.8976274,
            "question": "powerful",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "triangolare",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1519238134.2183902,
            "question": "triangular",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "acido",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1519238165.7056165,
            "question": "sour",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "easy",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1519238177.777754,
            "question": "facile",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "wet",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1519238195.4851656,
            "question": "bagnato",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "ampio",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1519238172.3695188,
            "question": "wide",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "shapes",
            "failed": 5,
            "lastAsked": 1519238208.353879,
            "question": "forme",
            "tried": 9
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tastes",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1519238189.6454766,
            "question": "i gusti",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "inexpensive",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1519238204.2051232,
            "question": "economico",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "very",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1519238206.5804064,
            "question": "molto",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "quantita"
            ],
            "answer": "quantit√†",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1519238175.4575815,
            "question": "quantities",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sottile",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1519238220.7047424,
            "question": "thin",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fresco",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1519238237.5966375,
            "question": "fresh",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "morbido",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1519238234.9209285,
            "question": "soft",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sizes",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1519238215.3057046,
            "question": "dimensioni (or) misure",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "luce",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1519238249.5087187,
            "question": "light",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "a few"
            ],
            "answer": "a few",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1519238251.6048694,
            "question": "qualche",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "economico",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1519238240.6368744,
            "question": "inexpensive",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "cattivo",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1519238247.3686404,
            "question": "bad",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "piccante",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1519238314.036368,
            "question": "spicy",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "lento",
            "failed": 3,
            "lastAsked": 1519238308.0237124,
            "question": "slow",
            "tried": 7
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "very"
            ],
            "answer": "much",
            "failed": 4,
            "lastAsked": 1519238319.1809623,
            "question": "molto",
            "tried": 8
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "quiet",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1519238267.0602727,
            "question": "tranquillo",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sporco",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1519238254.5727813,
            "question": "dirty",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "costoso",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1519238264.5964859,
            "question": "expensive",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "small"
            ],
            "answer": "little",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1519238261.5083086,
            "question": "poco",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "tutto"
            ],
            "answer": "tutto (or)completo, totale",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1519238269.8040757,
            "question": "whole",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sbagliato",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1519238339.2155797,
            "question": "wrong",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "rumoroso",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1519238334.2083242,
            "question": "noisy",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vuoto",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1519238344.0519943,
            "question": "empty",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "lungo",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1519238342.1354258,
            "question": "long",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "forme",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1519238329.2200348,
            "question": "shapes",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "local",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1519238322.9318292,
            "question": "locale",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "profondo",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1519238347.7711992,
            "question": "deep",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "whole",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1519238350.4516022,
            "question": "tutto (or)completo, totale",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "circolare",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1519238376.4076145,
            "question": "circular",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "giovane"
            ],
            "answer": "giovane / giovani",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1519238356.4923792,
            "question": "young",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "qualche"
            ],
            "answer": "a few",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1519238364.8276358,
            "question": "a",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "bianco",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1519238371.3523278,
            "question": "white",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "pieno",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1519238368.9923396,
            "question": "full",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "salato",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1519238358.3389754,
            "question": "salty",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "viola",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238360.1970637,
            "question": "purple",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dark",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238373.4396992,
            "question": "buio",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "arancione",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238390.519061,
            "question": "orange",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "circular",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238385.8394053,
            "question": "circolare",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "parts"
            ],
            "answer": "part",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238382.7593486,
            "question": "parte",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "light",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238387.86321,
            "question": "luce",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "correct",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238378.423282,
            "question": "corretto",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "quantities",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238392.8715117,
            "question": "quantit√†",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "qualita"
            ],
            "answer": "qualit√†",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238397.2352333,
            "question": "qualities",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "qualities",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238380.9187212,
            "question": "qualit√†",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "square",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238401.8989956,
            "question": "quadrato",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dirty",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238414.1624854,
            "question": "sporco",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fresh",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238410.4513261,
            "question": "fresco",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "facile",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238399.7402673,
            "question": "easy",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dry",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238408.8747354,
            "question": "secco",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "buono",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238404.1469045,
            "question": "good",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "parte",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238406.154881,
            "question": "part",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "colors",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238412.2668848,
            "question": "colori",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "soft",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238432.2950737,
            "question": "morbido",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "duro"
            ],
            "answer": "duro (or)difficile (difficult)",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238419.897693,
            "question": "hard",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "triangular",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238427.8951008,
            "question": "triangolare",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "quadrato",
            "failed": 2,
            "lastAsked": 1519238442.4143324,
            "question": "square",
            "tried": 6
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "thin",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238430.3988855,
            "question": "sottile",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tranquillo",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238417.330411,
            "question": "quiet",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "hard",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238421.6545823,
            "question": "duro (or)difficile (difficult)",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "heavy",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238424.886698,
            "question": "pesante",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "difficult",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238449.7304325,
            "question": "difficile",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sour",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238457.7703207,
            "question": "acido",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "alto",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238444.9986355,
            "question": "tall",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "yellow",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238447.2022777,
            "question": "giallo",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "tall",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238459.7625194,
            "question": "alto",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "giallo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238461.5063896,
            "question": "yellow",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "noisy",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238466.002485,
            "question": "rumoroso",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "piccolo",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238468.0580854,
            "question": "small",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "brown",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238475.2939506,
            "question": "marrone",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "red",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238471.658079,
            "question": "rosso",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "blu",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238480.6452973,
            "question": "blue",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "molto",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238482.9339895,
            "question": "very",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nuovo",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238470.0344546,
            "question": "new",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "strong"
            ],
            "answer": "powerful",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238477.421822,
            "question": "potente",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "grande",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238479.3336835,
            "question": "big",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "long",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238473.2390044,
            "question": "lungo",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "orange",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238490.4135602,
            "question": "arancione",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "fast",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238496.2133725,
            "question": "veloce",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "verde",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238494.3979836,
            "question": "green",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "locale",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238484.6541262,
            "question": "local",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "rosso",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238492.5764277,
            "question": "red",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "full",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238486.2943728,
            "question": "pieno",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "white",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238488.1332834,
            "question": "bianco",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "many",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238498.949737,
            "question": "molti",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "nero",
            "failed": 1,
            "lastAsked": 1519238542.5537324,
            "question": "black",
            "tried": 5
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "sweet",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238505.6017702,
            "question": "dolce",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "vecchio",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238503.7136447,
            "question": "old",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "grigio",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238501.429673,
            "question": "gray",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "black",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238535.537072,
            "question": "nero",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "expensive",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238508.5618942,
            "question": "costoso",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "gray",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238537.425526,
            "question": "grigio",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "spicy",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238539.4650867,
            "question": "piccante",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "big",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238556.109339,
            "question": "grande",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "good",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238546.2569606,
            "question": "buono",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "old",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238554.5850637,
            "question": "vecchio",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "straight",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238558.3175907,
            "question": "dritto",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "new",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238547.67313,
            "question": "nuovo",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "foreign",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238553.081257,
            "question": "straniero",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [
                "basso"
            ],
            "answer": "breve (or)corto (or)basso",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238550.5137239,
            "question": "short",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "salty",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238560.9967904,
            "question": "salato",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "dolce",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238564.9810147,
            "question": "sweet",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "young",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238570.9571693,
            "question": "giovane / giovani",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "colori",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238568.9647706,
            "question": "colors",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "veloce",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238567.1176937,
            "question": "fast",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "deep",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238578.940914,
            "question": "profondo",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "bad",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238562.925152,
            "question": "cattivo",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "short",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238574.3248146,
            "question": "breve (or)corto (or)basso",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "marrone",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238576.9885876,
            "question": "brown",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "clean",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238580.7727814,
            "question": "pulito",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "small",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238585.4486182,
            "question": "piccolo",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "difficile",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238583.6771486,
            "question": "difficult",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "purple",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238589.7687378,
            "question": "viola",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "green",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238587.3930268,
            "question": "verde",
            "tried": 4
        },
        {
            "alternates": [],
            "answer": "blue",
            "failed": 0,
            "lastAsked": 1519238591.2095108,
            "question": "blu",
            "tried": 4
        }
    ]
}